// src/db.js
export const quizData = [
    { id: 0, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz0', answer: 'answer0' },
    { id: 1, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz1', answer: 'answer1' },
    { id: 2, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz2', answer: 'answer2' },
    { id: 3, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz3', answer: 'answer3' },
    { id: 4, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz4', answer: 'answer4' },
    { id: 5, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz5', answer: 'answer5' },
    { id: 6, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz6', answer: 'answer6' },
    { id: 7, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz7', answer: 'answer7' },
    { id: 8, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz8', answer: 'answer8' },
    { id: 9, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz9', answer: 'answer9' },
    { id: 10, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz10', answer: 'answer10' },
    { id: 11, category: 'science', level: 'medium', question: 'quiz11', answer: 'answer11' }
    // 他のクイズデータ
];